Are you good?
称好吗 ?
Paris are good?
巴黎好呆?
T learn French for you!
我为你学法文
I want to live with Paris in you.
我好想跟和一起住在巴黎
But money I do not have.
可是我没有翁
Paris is world of love.
巴黎是爱情的世界
Without you Taipei is very sad.
没有炼，台北好寂寞
Work with my father and my mother.
我跟和爸爸和杂妈一起工作
Day after day, my life is same.
一天过一天 我的生活都是一样
I always think of you.
我一直想到尹
Imagine us on the streets of Paris.
想我们十个走在巴黎的街头
Anyway, I'm still practicing everyday.
呵，反正我还有在每天鲁翌
Hope I have a chance to speak to you soon.
希望可以有机会跟你讲一讲
So...call me back when you can.
那…就等你有空 再打电话给我好了
Okay, that's all for now.
0Kk，就这样
Bye-bye.
好，和拜拜
The moonlight shines...
月色照在
On an open road...
三线路
A breeze is blowing...
风吹微微
I wait for him..., but he's not there.
等待的人那没来
But my heart doesn't know...
心内真可疑
If he is coming.
想抹出彼个人
It sounds ridiculous
说起来有是可笑
But really...
不过
T haven't felt like this in a long time.
我很久没有这种感觉了
This woman has brought love back into my life.
这个女孩子让我知道 什么叫做炙爱
Think about it.
你想想看
All this other stuff: Protection...
以前啊，就是这样收保护费
Prostitution...
三七仔
Gambling...
诈赌啦
Running numbers, loan-sharking...
不然就是药头给人放高利贷
It's all meaningless to me now.
这哪有什么意思?
Brother Bao.
豹哥啊
I think you might be having...
你这种情形
Some kind of mid-life crisis.
就是人家在说的中年危机
‘You ever been to Hainan Island?
你有去过海南岛吗 ?
Never.
没去过
What are you going to do there?
那你去海南岛是要做什么
Enjoy life with her.
陪她好好过下半生
And grow old together.
一起慢慢变老
Oh, my South China Sea Girl.
噢一南海姑娘
Don't be so brokenhearted!
何必太过悲伤
Fuck off.
您娘啦
But Brother Bao...
不过，豹哥啊
Your real estate company is making good money.
你那间房屋仲介公司 不是做得好好的?
Yeah, it's doing well.
公司是赚钞没有错
Everyone knows that.
大家都知道
And it's clean.
但是，那个是非常乾兆的
But this other score...
若和后面这休
If we take care of that...
我如果处理得好
Brother Bao...
豹哥
Are you sure about this?
你真的确定你要这魔做?
When you get to my age...
唉，你到我这城数你就知道了
‘You just want to be happy.
散喜就好
Fuck off.
您娘咀
I don't understand.
我不慌
Excuse me, sorry.
不好意思，借遇一下
This isn't a library you know.
这和里可不是图书馆
I'm just flipping through this.
只是随便翻一翻而已
But you're here every night.
可是我每天都看你来这
Why don't you just buy it?
那你干嘛不买 ?
I don't know. I guess I'm just bored.
没有，就有点和无聊
‘You must be really bored.
那你还真乱聊
Yeah.
噢
I'm not making fun of you.
我不是在笑你噢
It's just that I see you in here a lot.
只是，我每天都在这壬看到你
Oh.
噢
Anyway, see you tomorrow.
那…明天见
Oh, okay.
噢，好啊
How are you?
炼还好吗 ?
T haven't spoken to you in a while.
好久都没有跟你讲到话了
If you get a chance
如果可以的话
Can you give me a call back?
还是打个电话给我好吗 ?
You're always in my heart.
你永下在我的心里
Good night, my little butterfly.
了晚安，我的小蝴蝶
About those four units...
现在那四问都是…
Right, four units, each 300 square meters.
大直那四问30坪左右的
Thad them appraised already.
都请银行估好价了
I start showing them next week.
下礼拜二礼拜四会有五个客户
It's all taken care of.
一次把它看完
Very good.
很好啊
Uncle, I got a handle on the real estate stuff.
二伯，房地产那录你不用扒心啦
But there are other things I'm capable of.
其实我绝对有能力做更多的事情
Kai, take this to Brother Bao.
小凯啊 ! 这类拿去给豹哥
Oh.
噢
Are you asleep?
你在发什么采啊
I'm fine.
没有啊
If there's anything I can help with...
所以啊，你另外一外要是有和缺…
Brother Bao.
豹哥
Kai, you're around a lot these days.
小凯，你最近常在这啊
Oh yeah, just helping out.
噢，没有啊 ! 就来帮忙
It's temporary.
只是新时的
I see.
这榜子啊
Actually, we could use a smart college boy.
其实我们那录也很需要大学生
It's okay, I've got plans already.
没有，和鹏哥，我自己有在计首
Well, if you need anything....
嗯，你如果有什么需要的话
Just let me know.
囊管跟我讲啊
Don't be shy.
不要客气
Sure. Thanks, Brother Bao..
好，谢谢豹哥
Enjoying that?
很好吃啊?
-Good luck. -Thanks.
-来，祝你得大痪啊 -好，谢谢
-Come again. -Sure.
-再来啊      -一定会的
Ma'am, I'd like to buy a scratcher.
阿桑，我要圈一张刊到乐
Sure, what kind?
你要哪一种的?
One "Dream Come True". One "Treasure Chest".
一张旺旺来，一张金包银好了
Okay.
好
The fortune god wishes you luck.
祝你得大痪虽
He hasn't been much help lately.
财神第最近好像都不太理我
No way.
怎订会
Come play more often.
你就是要常常来到
And he'll take good care of you.
财神繁他认识你 要中痪就很容易啊
Hey! Come back here!
干什么大走
Thugs!
死孩子
Come back!
大走
I'm going to get you!
你可啥你
Watch the hair!
头聂…头肾乱了
You little thugs!
你这死小孩
Running away!
走走走
Come back here!
好脆套走 ! 奏走
Come back!
大走
I don't understand.
我不慌
What are you reading?
你都在看什么书啊?
Just this.
就看这个啊
It's got a pronunciation guide.
他这上面都有音标可以照著念
So... you're teaching yourself French?
所以，你自己看书学法文喔?
Yeah.
嗯，对啊
Is it working?
有用吗?
I'm not sure.
好像没有
Maybe you should try something else.
那你应该要再去找其他的方法
Is something wrong?
发生什么事了吗?
Why haven't you called me?
为什么都没有打志话给我
I just want to know that you're okay.
我只是想知道你好不好而已啊
I miss you so much.
我好想你
T love you so much.
我好爱你
Goodbye.
再见
Fuck off!
您娘咀
-Don't run! = -Freeze!
-不要跑      -给我站住啊
Hey, don't run!
-不要跑
Fuck, what are you doing?
干 【本啥啦
Hey, be careful!
不要抓，不要抓
Let's get the little prick!
笑尾啊 ! 弄他啦
Someone's coming.
人来了，人来了
How may I help you?
请问需要帮忙吗 ?
Fuck you.
赛您娘啦
Did it go smoothly?
顺利吗 ?
Tran into some problems.
有状况啦
What? Cops?
怎样? 皮休咀?
Thid it. It's safe.
东西我先藏起来 不会让他们找到
Hey, this is my retirement fund.
和娩，我下半生泳泳就守这
What is it, Hong?
阿洪，干嘛?
Nothing. I just...
没有啊，我只是想襄
If there's nothing else I'm going home.
没事的话我先回去了
Wait for me outside.
你在外面等我一下
Okay.
好
Uncle, who was that?
二伯，那个人是锥?
Listen, Hong.
阿洪，我跟你讲啊
I'm getting ready to retire
我就准备退体了
And I've decided to leave all this to you.
所以我打算这站以和后就交给你了
No problem, Uncle.
没问题啊，二伯
But this lottery store shit...
像那个什么彩券行那种啊
It's beneath you. Cut it out.
没水准的事以和后就别干了
Understand?
知道咕?
But Uncle, you know...
可是二伯，你也知道
It was a real sweet score!
我们那一票真的干得很漂亮
Everything here could be yours.
这站赚的全部给你
That's not enough?
干嘛? 嫌少啊?
It's just that... I want to see a little action.
不是，我只是想 有了时候需要趣味趣味
Action?
趣味 ?
Okay, I understand.
好，我知道了
Say no more.
你不用再说服我了
So we're clear?
清楚了?
We're clear.
清楚了
Good.
清楚就好
What are you looking at?
看什么看 ?
Nothing.
没有啊
Hey, Kai.
嘿，小凯
Hey, Gao.
嘿，高
Thanks.
谢啦
So was Peach there tonight?
那桃子今天也在吗 ?
Yeah.
在啊
And?
然后啊 ?
Oh, we...
噢，我们噢
I'm working on it.
我有在那个啦
What's wrong?
怎庆啦 ?
Nothing.
嗯，没事啊
You still hungry?
你还饿不饭?
Yeah.
饿啊
Okay.
噢
Come with me now.
现在你跟我回去
I'll take care of this bastard first.
我把这的卒仔处理掉之和后
No!
套啦
How could you do this to me?
为什么你要人这样对待我?
Dinner's almost ready.
差不多可以准备吃唆
Ji-Yong.
基永
What did you say?
你刚刚说什么
I said dinner's ready.
我说可以准备吃了
But I'm heading out.
可是我要出去了耶
Okay.
吗
Hello? I'll be right down.
喂，好，我忆上下去
Wushing's downstairs.
吴愉在楼下了
Okay, I'm going then.
那我走唾
They were all wearing suits.
他们全部都穿那个西装
The color? Orange.
他们穿那个什么色? 啊 【橘子色
The were all quite handsome and polite.
大家看起来都很英俊 一表人才的样子
One of them said they wanted to buy one.
一个人进来就跟我说要圈
And started scratching. I was distracted.
就在那下乔刊刊，我也没去注意
And there was a...
然后就帮一下…
Don't worry, Ma'am. We'll take care of it.
老半娘，放心，我们会处理的
Thank you.
谢谢
Wait, I'm not done yet.
没有啦 ! 我还没说完啦
Next time we get a case like this, just shoot me.
下次再有这样的案子 麻烦你捅死我
Are you hungry?
肚子饿不能?
Let's grab something to eat.
去找东西吃
Okay, sir.
好啊，学长
Jack-knife one. Over.
长江一史
Sir, do you think they'll really come back?
学长 你真的觉得会有人回来吗?
‘You can count on it.
啊不然啊 ?
It's the big time for us.
我们这不是加模的
All right.
对厚
Here.
效…
Hello?
喂?
I'm working. Call you back later.
我现在在工作，晚是打给你
Sir, was that your girlfriend?
学长，你女朋友咀?了
Huh?
啊?
-Your girlfriend? -Huh?
-你女朋友啊 -啊?
Your chick?
妹啦
None of your business.
天你什么事啊?
Oh.
吗
It was just one of them!
其中之一啦
And I'm telling you, guys like us...
而且我告诉你，像我们这一种
We get all the chicks.
要妹多得数不完
Really?
真的喔 ?
Watch and learn.
多学著琶
Okay.
好
Stay focused.
专心工作
Whoever comes back, we'll grab them.
谁回来拿，我们就把他抓起来
Hey.
理 ov
Hi.
路
Hey, have you thought taking some classes?
你有没有想要去上课啊?
Um...
吗
I think it might be faster.
我觉得那榜应该会学比较快
I'm taking dance classes right now.
像我就在学跌舞咀
Have you ever heard of the Lindy Hop?
你有职过LindyHop吗 ?
The what?
什么啊?
It's a type of swing dance.
就是一种欣气手
Um...maybe I can just show you.
不然，我跳给你看喔
It goes something like this...
大概是人这样
Something like that.
类似的
Oh.
呵
Hey, that have some language classes there.
他们那站也有一些语言课
English, Japanese...
像是英文、日文…
They should have French too.
应该也有法文
I can get you a schedule.
不然下次我帮你拿一张课表
That's okay.
没关像啦
Really...
是吗
Hey, so are you going to France or something?
你是不是要去法国啊
Yeah.
对啊
Really?
真的喔 ?
My girlfriend's over there.
我女朋友现在在那儿
Oh.
吗
So you're studying French for your girlfriend?
所以你为你的女朋友 然后学法文 ?
Oh.
吗
That sounds romantic.
这样很浪漫
Really?
会吗 ?
Doesn't she think so?
她不这样沉得吗 ?
Hello?
喂?
Faye? Hi.
震徘呆，嘿
So, is everything okay?
所以，都还ok吗 ?
Oh
咀?
Me? I'm doing okay.
我吗，我还oK啊
Nothing much.
对啊，没什么事
What is it?
怎床了吗?
Why?
为什么 ?
What's wrong with you?
你是怎订摘的啦 ?
We don't have the money for that.
家里没这个负啦
I'll pay you guys back.
我会还你们的啦
What are you thinking, kid?
你在想什么啦，年轻人?
I don't know... I just need to get over there.
我知道 可是我就是要赶快明去啊
Forget about it! Just forget about it.
算了啦 ! 真的算了啦
Maybe this is all for the best.
说不定这榜对你比较好
Think about it.
再想一想啦
or why don't you go get a job?
或许去外面找一个工作做
We're not forcing you to work here.
我跟你老和爸也没有瘟望 你在这里帮忙啊
Right?
对不对
I'll close up. You guys can to upstairs.
我来收，你们先上去没关父
Don't dwell on it too much.
不要想那魔多
How much do you need?
你需要多少?
Just enough to get to Paris.
只要锡去巴黎就可以了
And maybe to stay out there for a while.
可能还需要在那录多待一阵子
Not a problem.
那没有问题
It's just that...
只是突然就这样
We had already made these plans.
我们本来都已经讲好了
No need to explain.
别跟我解释这一些
That's the way love goes.
感情本来就是这个样子
You'll figure it out.
以和后你习惯就好了
Thanks, Brother Bao
豹哥，谢谢
How long have I been eating at your restaurant?
我去你家吃类都吃这广多年了
I know you're good for it.
你，我信得过
Ah...the one that got away...
唉，年轻不懂珍惜，都错过了
It's nice to be in love, isn't it?
其实谈谈小继爱还不错的
Sir...
学长
Do you think we'll get to use our guns this time?
我们这次这个案子 有没有机会并到检啊
I can handle it, sir.
呵，学长，我一定可以的
What is it?
你说啊
What?
啥?
Okay, I understand.
好，我知道
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
你等在那不要动，我来处理
I said get out of here!
叫你回去你就回去
Kai, where are you going?
小凯，你要去哪里啊?
Oh,I have some stuff to do. I can't work tonight.
喔 ! 今天可能有点事 不能帮忙了
I'll be back later.
等一下就回来了
Hey, what are you here?
你来这干嘛?
I'm here to see Brother Bao.
我找豹哥
Brother Bao?
找豹哥咀?
He told me to come by.
他叫我来的
Sure you don't need help with anything?
确定没有事情要帮忙 ?
Uncle, he's here to see you.
二伯，他找你
Don't you have something to do?
你没事吧?
Oh, I have an apartment to show.
嗓，我约了人看房子
I better get going.
那我先去叶
Come, have a seat.
来 ，坐吧，坐吧
So are you all set?
都准备好了吗 ?
Yeah, just about.
差不多了
Good.
好
Thave a little favor I need to ask of you.
我还有个小事要请你帮忙
Oh, okay..
嚼，好
Sorry to trouble you.
麻烦你一下，就是呢
Ineed you to take something with you.
我有个小东西要带过去
Okay, okay.
嚼，好
Uh...Brother Bao, where is it?
豹哥，那…那个东西呢?
Oh, I need you to pick it up for me.
啊 ! 要你攻我去拿一下
Oh, okay. Sure.
咀!没问题
Don't worry, it's all taken care of.
别担心，都安排好了
Someone will give it to you.
到时候就有人把东西交给你了
This package is very important to me.
这东西非常的重要
Got it?
知道咕?
‘You must be very excited.
你现在应该很兴奋啊?
Oh, yeah.
嗯，对啊，对啊
But Brother Bao...
但是豹哥
What is it?
怎庆啦 ?
It's just...I don't know...
我不知道，我只是
Hey, is your flight all set, Kai?
那个…你机票订好了没有 ? 小凯
Yeah, I leave tomorrow morning.
咀，对啊 ! 明天早上
Do you need some extra cash?
要不要多带一卫钞 ?
No, I have enough.
不用，不用，金了
Good.
好
Hey, Peach.
嘿，桃子
Do you...
另，那个
What?
什么 ?
Do you know if we have more of these in stock?
你知道我们和后面还有这个吗 ?
I don't know. Go check in back
我不知道，你去后面看看啊
Oh, okay.
嚼，好啊
Thanks.
谢谢
No problem.
不会
Hey, Gao.
嘿，高
Hey.
理 ov
So I'm just about set.
我准备差不多了
I just came over to say bye
我只是过来跟你襄一声
Okay, let's go.
好啊 ! 那走啊
Go where?
要去哪 ?
To eat.
吃人饭啊
That's okay, really.
不用，不用，真的不用
I have some stuff to take care of.
我待会还有一点事啊
But you're leaving.
你都要走了
Hey, Peach.
嘿，桃子
We'll be back in an hour or so. Is that okay?
我们一十个小时和后就回来0k吗 ?
Oh.
吗
T only have two hours.
我只等两个小时吗
See? No problem.
看吧 ! 没问题啦
Okay. But I have to go pick something up first.
好啦 ! 可我待会要拿个东西
Look guys...
你们看看
He has this score...
现在有什么好处
And he's cutting us out of it.
他竟然也没想要分给我们
Aren't we brothers?
我们不是兄弟吗
Instead he has us showing shitty apartments all day.
一天到晚叫我们来豆什么小公寓
Brother Bao is almost finished anyway.
豹哥，已经差不多了
There's nothing to worry about.
真的不用怕
If anything happens, the kid takes the blame.
葛一出了什么事 统统推到那个小子身上去
We make a sweet score, someone else takes the fall.
我们干一票 还有人当替死鬼，多好
Don't you guys want to make a big score?
你们不是也想要干一票大的吗 ?
Here's your chance!
现在机会来啦
Mr. and Ms. Cheng...
郊先生，部太太
Excuse us.
不好意思
What do you think?
你们还满意吗?
Actually, our last tenants really loved this place.
其实我们上一个房客 也非常喜欢这里
But the husband got caught cheating.
只是和后来那位先生不小心偷吃
Things got messy and...
然后他还有外遇…
We can install your new washer and dryer in a few days.
我们过雨天 再儿你们装洗衣机还有烘乾机
We'd like to think about it some more.
我们大概膛要再考虑一下
Very wise, very wise.
明智，明箱
But I can assure you for a place like this.
其实这样的人条件，这榜的价炙
The price is quite reasonable.
真的很实在
Here's my card.
这是我的名月
If you need anything, don't hesitate to call.
您看有什么需要 再打上面电话给我就好
Okay.
好好好
Thanks.
谢谢
Morons.
土炮啦
Anyway, I'll be with Brother Bao.
反正我人会一直待在豹哥淮关
That way he won't suspect anything.
这样他就不会怀疑
Once you make the grab
你们一拿到东西呢
Bring it your aunt's place.
就去你阿姨家
I'll meet up with you guys there.
我再跟你们会合
Sweet, eh?
水吗?
Sweet!
水啦
Sir, do you want a piece?
学长，你要不要来一月 ?
I'm not hungry.
我不钱
But sir, it's really good.
学长 ! 这真的很好吃
I said I'm not hungry.
我说不饭了
Sir, are you sure?
学长，你确定 ?
Oh.
唤
Sir, look!
学长，你看
Wushing, move it!
吴和内，你在干嘛 ? 快是啦
Hey, Kai.
小咒
Password.
暗疆
Huh?
呵?
Password!
暗线啦 !
Brother Bao told me to come pick up something...
是那个豹哥他叫我来拿个东西…
If you don't give me what I need...
你没有把东西交给我
How can I give you what you need?
我怎订把东西交给你啦?
Password.
暗号啦
But I...
可是我…
I'm just messing with you.
我跟你开玩笑的啦
Don't be such a dipshit.
你怎庆那麻古椎
Be careful with this.
拿好咀
This is it?
就这榜啊?
What should we do, sir?
啊! 学长，我们怎庆办?
Follow them!
追啊
Hey, Gao.
嘿，高
Let's go.
好了，走吧
Did you get it?
拿到了吗 ?
Yeah, no problem.
拿到了，没问题啦
Let me see it.
借看一下啦
You can't handle it.
不要，你很土
No way, it's my gun, not your gun...got it?
不要，现在就是 我有Gun你没GCun，怎庆样
-Please? -No.
-和拜旗好不好? -不要啦
Okay, let's eat
好了，去吃吧
Okay.
吗
Where do you want to start?
那我们要从哪狠开始?
You decide
你决定
Okay.
好啊
So...what are you going to do when you get to Paris?
那你去巴黎要先干嘛?
Get Faye back.
去把罪乔追回来啊
Those dumplings are pretty good.
前面水秀包还满好吃的
Okay.
是吗
What is it?
干嘛?
Nothing.
吗，没有
Do you know her?
认识吗 ?
Sort of.
算吧
Okay.
好啊
Hey, wait...
等一下
Hi.
路
T haven't seen you around recently.
好翁天没看到你
Yeah, I've been a little busy.
对啊，最近比较忙
Oh yeah...
吗，对了
I was at dance class the other day.
我前绑天去上跳舞课的时候
And I checked it out for you.
有顺便医你看了一下
I think they do have French classes...
他们的法文课好像是在…
It's okay. I'm going to Paris.
没关像啦 ! 因为我要去巴黎了
Really? When?
是咀， 什么时候啊?
Um, tomorrow morning.
咀，明天早上
Oh.
吗
I probably won't get this tood for a while.
我们想说以和后可能没机会了
So I better eat it while I can.
所以…就超快来这站吃一吃
Do you want to get something to eat?
对啊，要不要再吃一点东西
Oh, this is Gao.
嚼，这是高高
This is...
这是…
I'm Susie.
我是Susie
She, um, works at the bookstore.
她在那个…韦店工作
Can you guys get me some dumplings?
你们帮我多买交个
I'm going to go get a sausage roll.
我去那末买大肠包小肠
Oh.
吗
So are you here alone?
称一个人啊?
Yeah, I'm just on my way to class.
嗯，等一下要去上课
Seems like you take a lot of classes.
你好像很常上很多课的榜子
T like to keep myself busy.
就是想让自己忙一束
Please don't cut in line.
先生，不要插队好吗
Excuse me. You're coming with us.
歹势虽 ! 你跟我们来一下
We'll be right back.
我们等一下就回来
What do you want?
你们要干嘛?
-Do you have it? -Hand it over.
-东西在你那姑 -交出来啦
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你们在讲什么
Show him what we're packing
让他看看啦
Don't run, Police!
不要跑，警察
Don't run!
不要跑
Hey, where did you go?
你大刚跑去哪?
Come on.
走啦
Stand still!
站住
What's wrong with you?
搞什么啦 !
Nothing, I was just thinking...
没有，我只是想说
It was a little too crowded over there.
那先人太多了，就不要在那杀
Are you running from someone?
你是不是在躲蕉啊?
No.
没有啊
Fuck.
干
What now?
现在怎订办 ?
Hey, isn't that his friend?
嘿，那是不是他朋友 ?
Are you hiding from those two guys?
你是不是在躲刚才那十个人?
No, I don't even know who they are.
没有，我根本不认识
Right. I'll see you later.
那我走唾
Wait a second.
等一下
What?
干嘛?
Let's just hang out here for now.
没有，我们可以在这站等一下
What about Gao?
那高高史?
-Let's go. -Oh.
-走啦        -吗
Gao!
一 一 口。 冲 吏 癌
What?
干嘛?
Excuse us. Coming through.
不好意思，借遇一下
Excuse us.
不好意思
What's going on?
发生什么事了?
Gao.
一 一 口。 冲 吏 癌
Excuse us, sorry.
不好意思，借遇一下
Where are we going?
我们要去哪 ?
Shut the fuck up and get in.
干，你闭跑啦 ! 进去
Who were those guys?
他们是谁啊?
They're...uh...
就…
Was your friend just kidnapped?
你朋友是不是被他们抓走?
No.
没有啊
What are you doing?
称要干嘛?
Calling the police.
我要报警
Oh.
吗
Wait, you can't do that!
等一下，不能报警啦
Why not?
为什么 ?
I'm sure it's just a misunderstanding.
这麻该不是什么大问题啦
Seriously, don't do that.
真的不行啦
What's this all about?
你是不是知道什么啊?
I don't know.
我不知道啊
Fine. Go ahead and call.
好啦 ! 你打嘛
Hello, please connect me to the police.
喂，不好意思，我要报警
Hey, please don't do that.
等一下，真的不行啦
Hold on, listen to me.
好啦 ! 等一下，代匠我讲嘛
Maybe it have something to do with this.
可能是因为这个啦
Let me explain.
你匠我解释嘛
Okay. Explain.
好好好，你襄
-Back to the Palace? -Yeah.
-去皇家咀?       -咽
What about him?
那他呢?
Oh, you can just drop me off here.
嚼，我在这外下车就好了
I'm hungry.
唉哮 ，我肚子好饿喔
Aren't you guys hungry?
你们肚子都不版的虽
Yeah, but is there anything good around here?
饿啊 可是这站有什么好吃的吗 ?
How would I know?
我怎么知道 ?
I know a pretty good dumpling place nearby.
我知道前面有一癌 还不错的水稻店
I don't know, okay?
我也不知道啦
I'm just trying to get to Paris to see my girlfriend.
反正我就是想襄 这样可以去巴黎找我女朋友
Well, where did the package come from?
那东西哪里来的?
I was picking it up for someone.
是别人叫我帮他拿的啦
Who?
谁?
Brother Bao.
豹哥啊
I'm borrowed some money from him to get to Paris.
他借我钞让我可以去巴黎的
Brother Bao?
豹哥?
Yeah. I was desperate.
嗯，我真的没闪法嘛
I don't know how he's involved in all this.
我也不知道 他跟那些人有什么天像
Well what does he do?
那他是干嘛的啊?
Real estate.
房地产
Okay, I'll try calling him.
好啦，我现在打给他
I don't buy it!
哈，骗衣
I'll get it.
我来
Hello?
咀
Hello, may I speak to Brother Bao?
喂，请问豹哥在吗 ?
May I ask who's speaking?
请问哪里找?
Of course, how can I help you?
是啊，是啊，有什么事吧 ?
Oh, no. I just really need to talk to him.
呢，不是，我有点事情要跟他讲
Do you know when he'll be back?
请周你知道他什么时候回来吗 ?
I don't have that information on me right now.
可是我东西现在没有带在身上
But...I really need to speak to him.
不是，我有和急事要找他
I'll tell you what... go ahead and send me a brochure.
好啦，好啦 不然你把资料直接寄给我
Okay, let's keep in touch.
好，再联络
Hello?
咀
Credit-card scam.
诈骗集团
I think Brother Bao is busy.
豹哥好像在忙
So?
所以呢?
I don't know.
不知道
Let's just open it.
那我们把他打开看看
-No -Let me see it.
-不行啦       -我看一下
What's in here?
这和里面是什么啊?
I don't know.
不知道
Don't you think it's a little strange?
不觉得很奇怪吗 ?
‘You have no idea what you're delivering.
不知道什么就随便答应别人
What were you thinking?
你到底在想什么啊?
What is it?
怎庆啦 ?
That guy.
那个人
-You recognize him? -No.
-你认识吐? -不认识啊
Police!
警察
What is he yelling about?
他在喊什么啊?
I don't know
不知道
‘You two!
你们十个
-What should we do? -Run!
-怎订办?      -走
Hey!
咀
Hey, wait for me!
等我
Hurry!
快
You two, stop!
你们两个不要跑
Stop!
站住
Okay!
好啦
I'm a police officer!
我是警察
Excuse me.
不好意思 ，不好意思
Kids, no running in the subway!
同学，捷运站内禁止奔跑吗
Sir, no running in the subway!
先生，捷运站内禁止奔跑
Hey, I think we ditched him.
我们好像思掉他了
Yeah, great.
那很好啊
Hey, where are you going?
你要去哪啊?
Get out!
出来
I, Howard, promise I will also love Mandy!
我，谢豪一定会一草子疼惜曼曼
That will never change!
永束都不爸心
Will be with Howard forever!
一华子都不会离开谢豪
Auntie, we're going upstairs.
阿姨，我们上去唆
Oh.
咽，嗯
Fuck! These are pretty good.
干 ! 这真的很好吃耶
How much longer do we have to wait?
我们还要等多久啊
A little while, just sit tight.
没那麻快，膛要等一下
I'm sorry
对不起
I don't know what's going on either.
我真的不知道 现在到底怎订一回事
How did you get yourself involved in this?
我不懂你为什么把自己搞成这样
I don't know, I was just trying to get to Paris.
我不知道，我只是想去巴黎而已
That's all.
就这样啊
‘You couldn't think of an easier way?
但是真的有必要弄成这样吗 ?
It seemed reasonable at the time.
我那时候也觉得还好啊 !
I'm sure it did.
我想也是
What now?
现在怎订办 ?
What about Gao?
高高怎么办 ?
Kai...
小咒
This way!
那里
Hurry!!
快点啊
Police! Stop running!
警察 ! 不要跑
This way!
快，这站，这站
What are you doing?
干嘛?
Dance or we're going to get caught!
快跳，不然会被发现
Come on! Dance!
快点啦，跳啊
Okay.
好啦
You're doing it wrong.
不是那样跳啦
-Does it matter? -Yes
-有差吗 ?      -有
Forward.
往前
Worry about yourself.
姨你的
Like this.
像这样啊
Here.
这壬
Hey, where is he going?
他去哪啊
I think we can go now.
应该可以走了吧
Oh, okay.
嚼，好啊
Sir, I think you have the wrong person.
先生，你是不是认错人了…
Uncle, I have an apartment to show.
二伯，我要去带客人了
Now? This late?
现在? 三更半夜了
It was difficult to schedule.
很准款待
This is the only time they were available.
客人说现在才有空
I better get going!
那我先去叶
I don't want to be late.
快来不及了
Nice moves back there.
刚刚跳的不错
Pretty bad right?
很酿吧 ! 对不对?
There's room for improvement.
是有进步的空间啦
So what now?
现在呢?
I don't know.
我也不知道
Why you need to get over there so badly?
我不知道你为什么 那床急著要过去
Didn't you say that she's waiting for you?
你不是说她在那里等你吗 ?
Yeah. I guess so.
嗯，对啊 ! 是吧
Actually, she doesn't even know I'm coming.
其实，她根本不知道我要过去
You're kidding, right?
你在开玩笑吧?
We talked about going to Paris together.
我们那时候就有说好 要一起去巴黎
And then?
然后呢 ?
I guess she decided I should just stay in Taipei.
她可能觉得我留在台北比较好吧
I thought that if I could get over there somehow.
反正，我想说不管怎样就先过去
At least I would have that.
至少还去过了
I don'thave a whole lot going for me here.
我待在这下我也不知道在干什么
Draw!
自摸
Flush! Red dragon, three seasons, mixed suits!
庄家连一拉一和红中三花混一色
Wiped you out!
十台
Fuck! We're not playing for money!
干 ! 我们又没有拿翁
I told you guys...I have mahjong skills.
我刚刚就说过啦 ! 我以前照三餐打的
What are you wearing?
那你穿这干嘛?
Oh, I forgot to take it off.
没啊，忘了腕了
What a crappy job.
你做这个没出息啦
Hello and welcome, please come again.
坎迎光临，谢谢光上临
Good impression.
你学超像的妇
Shit yeah.
器和爸
Ijust got drafted though.
没有啦，要去当兵了啦
Fuck.
干
You got a girlfriend?
那你有妹吗 ?
Better hit that while you still can!
记得上于前要多打绑炮啦
No. I don't have a girlfriend.
没有啦，没有什么妹啦
But I'm working on it.
但是，就有在那个啦
Working on what?
哪个啦 ?
Nothing.
没有啦
Who's the girl?
那妹仔是谁啊?
Co-worker.
同事啊
What's her name?
她叫什么名字 ?
Peach.
桃子
Oh...Peach.
咀，桃子
So cute.
卡哇伊啊
Yeah.
对啊
How much longer do you have?
那你什么时候要去?
Not much longer.
差不多了
Does she know you're leaving?
那她知道你要去当兵了吗?
No.
不知道
Fuck! When she hears that...
干，女生要是贡到这个
Her bra will fly right off
奶章马上有下来啊
Really?
真的吗?
Just tell her...
不然你就跟她说
"Girl, I'm going off to the army..."
妹仔，我去当兵了
"T want you to know..."
我只是想要让你知道
"T won't stop thinking about you".
我会在那里想
That's how it's done.
人这样就对了
Definitely. You're in. No problem.
对啦，这样讲就没有问题了
Really?
真的吗?
How do you think he ever gets laid?
不然你以为 他怎订每次都把得到妹?
Actually, I've never even been in the army.
其实我根本不用当兵
Damn.
妈的
Playing mahjong?
打麻将啊?
Hey, Hong
味，阿洪
I want to play, who's winning?
我也要打，谁赢?
Who's this moron?
这土炮是谁?
We grabbed him.
这我们抓来的啊
Where's the package?
东西呢?
Oh.
吗
We had kind of a setback.
我们遇到一是状沉
But his friend has it.
可是在他朋友那婉
Right, so we were thinking...
对，所以我们就想说
Who told you guys to think?
想什么 ? 说什么 ?
If we grabbed him...
就我们先把他抓来
What is this? A picnic?
你们还在野餐啊!
I said get the package.
叫你们拿东西
But you bring back this moron!
抓个土炮回来
I can't believe you guys are my crew.
我怎订会被你们跟到啊 !
Our bad, Hong.
歹势啦，阿洪
Yeah, sorry Hong.
对不起啦，阿洪
Sorry, Hong.
对不起
It's okay, it's okay.
没关像，没关像
We'll just have to adapt to the circumstances.
只要我们重新掌握到状沉
We can still make this a successful score.
我们还是可以把事情顺利完成
Hey, Gao?
喂，高?
Hey Kai, it's me, Gao.
喂，小凯，我是高高
I know it's you! Are you okay?
我知道啊，你还好吧 ?
It's Gao.
是高高
Hey, Gao.
一 一 口。 冲 吏 癌
Not bad.
还好啊
Where are you?
你现在到底在哪里啊?
Hey.
咀
You have thirty minutes to get me the package.
我腿你30分钾之内 把东西交给我们
Huh?
啊?
Or there's going to be a dead body at bottom of the rive
不然你就等著去河录捞屁体咀
Dead body?
屁…册?
What do you want me to do?
那你要我怎订做嘛?
You know the Yongfu Bridge?
永福地下道，有没有
Uh-huh.
河的另外一亲
So...walk forward a little bit.
然后你就往前走一点
Walk forward a little bit more.
再往前走一点
And then...on your right...
然后…右外
There's an empty lot on the right.
右外有一埃空地
Just wait for us there.
你就在那姑等我们就好了
Okay, I'll be right there.
好好好，我马上过去
I'm warning you! Come alone. No cops.
我警告你虽 一个人来咀 ! 不要报警
Or there will be a dead body in the river!
不然你就要捞屁体虽
Okay, I understand.
好好好，我知道
Just hold on, I'll be there.
你等我一下，等我一下
Tie him up now please.
先把他乡起来啊
Oh, okay.
嚼，好啊
What?
怎庆榜了 ?
They want to exchange the package for Gao.
他们要拿高高来交换
What are you going to do?
那现在怎订办 ?
Really?
是吗!
I guess I should take care of this myself.
我就自己处理好了
You're really going alone?
你真的要一个人去喔 ?
Probably.
大概吧
Hey.
咀
I'm think it might be better if there's two of us.
我在想说，雨个人一起去 会不会比较好?
‘You sure you want to come?
你确定要去吗 ?
Okay.
可以啊
‘You sure you're okay?
你确定…你oK ?
Thanks so much for listening.
谢谢你陪我聊那庆久
I'm just glad I can be here for you.
跟你讲话我也很开心
So...I guess this is goodnight?
那…就晚安嗓
Goodnight.
晚安
Ji-Yong, what are you doing here?
基永，你怎庆会在这?
Ji-Yong?
基永?
Who is he?
他是谁啊?
Didn't you see the note I left?
我不是有留纸人条给你吗 ?
I saw it. But who's he?
我看啦 ! 但他是谁啊?
A friend.
朋友啊
Hi, I'm Raymond.
路 ! 我是Raymond
-A friend? -Hey.
-朋友 ?         -歼
That's right.
对啊
Oh yeah?
是吗?
Hey, why don't you calm down?
你不要那魔激动
IT am calm!
我没有激动啊
Don't do that!
别这样
Raymond, are you okay?
Raymnond，你还好吧 ?
I'm okay, no need to worry.
我没事，我ok，不用担心我
What did you push him for?
你干嘛推他啊?
He started it.
是他先动手的咀
I barely touched you.
有没有那庆严重啊?
We were just talking, that's it.
我们只是聊天 没什么 ! 就这样而已
-Although... -Raymond!
-牙然…             -Raymond
Yuan finally realizes you're not worth it
姐姐现在知道你不值得
Is that true?
真的吗?
‘Yuan, tell him.
媛媛，告诉他啊
Stay out of it.
天你什么事啊?
I'm sorry!
对不起啦
Yuan, wait...
奶奶…等一下
T already told you.
我已经跟你说过
I need time to think things over.
我需要时间好好想一想
Hey, your phone's ringing.
你手机结了
I know.
我知道
At least I'm getting Gao back.
至少我们还把高高救回来
I've gotten so used to waiting.
反正都等那麻久了
I'll just be stuck here a little longer.
最惨就是继续待在这亲
Being stuck here isn't so bad.
我觉得待在这里也不错啊
Where's the package?
东西呢?
Where's my friend?
我朋友呢?
Where's Gao?
高高呢?
Who?
谁啦?
My friend.
我朋友啊
Hand it over.
东西交出来咀
What are you doing?
你干嘛?
What are you doing? Let her go!
你干嘛?放并她
Why did you hit me?
打我干嘛?
Leave him alone! Hand it over!
把他放并，东西拿出来啦
Just give us the package, okay?
你们把东西拿出来就好啦
Did you hear me?
有了到没?
Okay, just take it easy.
好，你不要那麻激动啦
Idiot.
智障
Why did you have to hit me?
你打我干什么啦 ?
Let's go!
走了啦
Are you okay?
你有没有怎样?
My nose is broken!
我鼻子断了啦…
It's not broken.
没有断啦
But it will probably be swollen.
可是…等一下可能会很用
Gao's gone, the package is gone.
高高怎订办? 东西又掉了
I'm finished.
完蛋了啦
Hey, where are you going?
称要去哪 ?
Wait for me!
等一下啦
Susie, wait for me!
Susie，等我一下啦
What are you doing?
你干嘛?
There has to be one!
一定有
What?
什么 ?
Look!
你看
That's not a good idea.
这不太好吧
Aren't you going a little fast’?
你会不会骑太快啦 ?
Well done, we're all set.
这壬处理好，大家就类啦 !
Sir, where have you been?
学长，你去哪里啦 ?
Where is he?
他在哪?
Inside.
里面
Get down.
下来
Back to the Palace?
回去皇家吗 ?
Fuck, that was lame.
干，超衰的
Hello?
咀
Hey, uh... Kai.
那个小凯
How's everything going?
那儿怎床样，一切顺利吧?
Brother Bao, I've been trying to reach you!
豹哥，我有打给你
What's wrong? Did you have the package?
怎庆啦 ! 那个东西拿到了吗 ?
Yeah, I did...but someone's after me!
有 【我有!可是有人在追我
They grabbed my friend too!
他们还抓了我的朋友
Who?
谁?
I don't know! They were all wearing orange suits.
我不知道啊 ! 他们都穿桶色的西装
But you still have the package?
东西在不在你那嘛?
Yeah...I still have it.
还在我这外啊 !
-But they... -Okay, listen to me.
-可是他们… -好好好，我跟你讲
Just get yourself to the airport.
你就区我的话，乖冬到机场
I'll take care of everything else.
其他事我会夭理，知道了吗 ?
But Brother Bao, you don't understand.
豹哥，你可能不知道
Things are a little messed up right now.
现在状况真的有一点乱
Don't worry, just do what I said.
你就照我的话去做 不要想那魔多
-But Brother Bao... -Safe travels.
-不是啦 ! 豹哥 -好 ! 一路顺风
Brother Bao, wait...
豹哥，等一下…
What?
怎庆啦 ?
Hey, watch the road!
你看前面路
Hello! You've reached Hong's cell phone.
哈唾 !【 您现在打的 就是我阿洪的手机
I'm sorry that I'm unable to take your call...
真对不起，我现在不方便…
Hey, this is Brother Bao.
喂，我豹哥哎 !
Have you seen my boys there tonight?
你有看我那儿个孩子没 ?
Okay.
好好好
What?
安怎?
Let's go!
走
Let's go, let's go.
走了，走了
Excuse me, ma'am.
不好意思，老问娘
Did you just see someone run in here?
你刚才有看到做个人走进来吗 ?
Quicky? Three hundred.
休息三百
Oh, we're not, uh...
没有要那个啦
Eight hundred for the night.
若是要过夜八百
Okay, thanks.
好，谢谢
Does she know that you like her?
那她知道你喜欢她吗 ?9
No.
不知道
Why not?
为什么 ?
Because I get so nervous around her.
因为…每炊看到她我就很紧张
So you must really like her.
那你真的很喜获她
So why don't you tell her that you like her?
那你要不要跟她说你很喜欢她
I've thought about it.
我有想过啦
I think being in love is a beautiful thing.
我党得喜散一个人 是一件很美好的事情
But you have to be brave.
要勇敢一点
And be prepared for rejection.
要抱著被拒绝的心态
Like a man.
像个男人一样
Hey, Hong.
味，阿洪
Did you get it?
拿到了吗 ?
We got it.
拿到了
We're leaving now, Hong.
阿洪，那我们先走唆
Hold on, hold on.
等一下，等一下
Despite a few minor setbacks
引然这一次出了一点小状况
And a little miscommunication on my part.
我承认是我交代不锡清楚
We still managed to make a sweet score.
但是我们这一票 真的做得非常漂亮
Excellent.
很好，很好
Oh...
虽…
It was a good try, Hong.
阿洪，你真的已经很努力的啦
Right.
理 ov
You're still our Hong.
你还是我们的阿洪
Yeah.
对啊
Where are you three morons going?
你们三个土炮要去哪里啊?
There's no point anymore.
这事情没意思啊
Oh yeah, you can have this back.
对啦，这东西还给你啦
Sorry, Hong.
歹势，阿洪
What are you looking at?
看什么看 ?
Close call.
好险虽
Hear anything?
有没有?
It's probably not this one.
应该不是这问
Hey, be careful.
你小心一哑
Wait for me here.
你这壬等一下，我上去一下
Hey, noodle boy.
实下的
What is this?
这怎订回事?
Why did Brother Bao give this to you?
豹哥给你这个干什么?
I don't know.
我不知道啊
He doesn't know.
他不知道
Someone told him to bring it to Paris.
是有人叫他攻忙带去巴黎
Paris?
巴黎…?
Did that hurt?
会不会痛 ?
No.
不痛
I don't believe it.
怎庆可能…
There has to be something.
一定有
What are you doing?
你干嘛?
Shut up.
不要吵
Hey, what are you doing?
仇，你干嘛
Come on.
就不相信
Where is it?
在哪里?
French lessons? What the hell?
法文课 ? 什么啊?
It makes no sense.
没道理啊
Brother Bao gave you his photo.
豹哥把他的照片给你
To take to Paris...
叫你带去巴黎
That's Brother Bao?
那是豹哥?
Please be quiet.
你不要讲话
So tell me again what's really going on?
你还是乖乖的告诉我 到底发生什么事?
I don't know. Really.
我不知道啦，真的啦
Hong.
阿洪
Uncle.
二伯
What's wrong with you kids?
你这和孩子到底是在想什么 ?
You don't listen to anything I say.
怎么讲的话都不要区
Kai
小咒
Shouldn't you be on your way to the airport?
你不是乖乖的应该去机场了吗 ?
You can go to Paris now.
你可以去巴黎啦
It's cause...
那是因为…
Oh...
咀…
Nicely done!
你干的好事啊
Uncle, I was just...
二伯，我只是想说…
You wanted a big score, huh?
先干休大的，对吧
You think I'd hand over anything important
我告诉你，这魔重要的事情
To this dipshit?
会交给这种菜锅吗?
I already took care of the real package.
真正的货我早就不理好了
Police! Freeze!
警察 ! 别动
Put the gun down!
把枪放下
It's fake.
假的!
-Put it down! -Put it down!
-放下         -放下
Put it down.
放下
Huh.
中
Go!
走啊
Sir, are you okay?
学长，你没事吧?
Hey!
理 ov
What about us?
我们怎度办啊?
Can you get your hands free?
你手聂得开吗 ?
It's not tied too tightly.
他好像没有岂很紧
Can you try?
你也可以试看看吗 ?
Okay.
好
Gao, come help!
高高，来帮忙啦
Oh.
吗
Did you get it?
可以吗?
Are you okay?
你还好吧
I'm okay.
还好啊
You guys?
你们 ?
You take care of everything?
事情都处理好了2?
I'm supposed to be retiring.
念爸都要退休了
No more of this shit.
还摘这款
I'm telling you, I didn't do anything.
我警告你喔 ! 我什么事情都没有做
Where are you taking me now?
你现在要带我去哪里?
Back to the station?
回警察局对不对 ?
You know, I would make a good cop.
我也可以当警察
What do you think?
你觉得我去考警察怎条榜 ?
Are we going in the cop car?
我们现在要坐警车吗 ?
I want to ride shotgun.
那我要坐前面
Hey, take it easy.
咀，轻一点
Aren't you coming?
你不上于吗 ?
Sir, everyone's gone.
学长，都跑走了
No sign of the kids either.
那些小鬼都不见了
All I found was this.
我只找到这个
Come on, get in. Let's go.
上车 ! 走唆
What should we do now?
那现在怎订办 ?
Go back to the real estate office?
我们要不要回房地产公司啊?
Hello!
哈唆?
Sir, are you okay?
学长，你还好吧 ?
I'm fine.
我没事
Get in the car. Let's go.
那我们上车啦，回去唆
You have time to get to the airport?
那你飞机还超得上吗?
Oh, I think so.
吗，还可以啊
Hey, are you guys hungry?
仇，你们饿不能 ?
A little.
有一点
You want to get something to eat, Gao?
高高，要不要再去吃一是东西?
Oh, no I'm stuffed.
吗，不用，我好饮虽
Huh?
啊?
I should head back, Peach is waiting for me.
我该回去工作了 桃子还在店里等我
Oh.
吗
Hey, tell me where you get sent.
嘿，你抽到哪里再跟我讲
Take care.
不要变策
Okay, I'm going now.
好啦，那我走唾
Bye bye.
拜拜
I didn't know it was so late already.
我都不知道已经这麻晚了
It's okay.
没关像
I should go home anyway
我…还是回家好了
But I thought you were hungry.
可是你不是想吃东西吗?
Yeah...
是啊
But it's getting kind of late.
可是真的有点晚了
And...you should get going too.
而有全，你应该也差不多了吧
Hey, I know where we can go.
效，我知道吃什么了
Peach.
桃子
I thought you said only a few hours?
你不是说雨个小时吗?
I'm sorry.
对不起啦
What took you so long?
怎么那庆久啊?
Tran into a few problems.
嚼，我刚刚遇到一点事情
Well, you're covering my next two shifts.
那接下来十班都给你代吗
Okay.
好
There's more stuff that needs to be stocked.
后面还有些货膛没上
Peach.
桃子
Hmm?
嗯?
What?
什么 ?
See you tomorrow.
明天见
Bye bye, Gao.
咖，高高，和拜拜
Bye bye.
拜拜
What is this place?
这和里是哪里啊?
Give me a minute.
你等我一下
Sorry, we're out of dumplings.
不好意思，没有水通了
It's okay.
是吗
‘You sure you have time?
你这样来得及吗 ?
I think so.
吗，还好
I just have to grab my stuff upstairs.
待会再去楼上拿个东西就好了
How is it?
还可以吐?9
Not bad.
还不错啊
What are you smiling about?
你在笑什么 ?
Nothing.
没有啊
I was thinking about you bugging me at the bookstore.
你知道，炼之前在书店的时候 快把我给烦死了
Yeah right.
才没有啊
‘You were just someone to talk to.
我只是随便聊聊
Oh.
吗
Wait a second.
等我一下
So I...
咖， 我…
I should...
那我…